<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>Eclipsed</name>
    <directory>eclipsed</directory>
    <id>2927849284</id>
    <description>Play as Nadab &amp; Abihu - explosive brothers or as Unbidden - shadow spirit

[h1]Features:[/h1]
[list]
[*] +4 characters
[*] +50 items
[*] +20 trinkets
[*] +40 consumables
[*] +3 challenges
[*] +16 curses
[*] +2 new beggars
[/list] 

[hr][/hr] 
[h1] Characters: [/h1]
2 new characters with unique gameplay, as well as their tainted versions with no less exciting features.

[h1] Nadab [/h1]
Play as Nadab, manage your max.health to get more opportunities to [b]detonate[/b].
Unique synergies with bomb items.
Abihu will accompany you, distracting enemies from you.

[h1] Abihu - &quot;The Profane&quot; [/h1]
Play as Abihu and use body of your brother Nadab to blow up your enemies.
Abihu can't cry. But don't worry, he's very [b]flammable[/b].

[h1] Unbidden [/h1]
Unbidden cannot die until he is completely [b]broken[/b].
Collect wisps to get real items on the next floor.
Build an array of active items at your disposal, swapping between them with CTRL.


[h1] Tainted Unbidden - &quot;The Infinite&quot; [/h1]
Play as the immortal spirit who eludes death.
Collect wisps instead of items, and materialize them with your pocket item, Threshold.
Build an array of active items at your disposal, swapping between them with CTRL.
Use your unique offensive ability - aura, to attack enemies all around you at once.
Raise your stats and collect unique tear effects to make your aura more effective.
Don't let the sands of the eternal hourglass catch up to you, or you'll rewind to the start...


[h1] Unlocks: [/h1]
Earn all 12 completion marks on new characters to unlock new stuff.
Also don't forget about the new challenges, which also have new items.

[h1] Curses: [/h1]
 [table]
    [tr]
        [th]Curse[/th]
        [th]Effect[/th]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Curse of the Pride[/td]
        [td]50% chance to enemies become champion (except boss)[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Curse of the Magician[/td]
        [td]25% chance to shoot homing enemy tear (except boss)[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Curse of the Emperor[/td]
        [td]remove exit door from boss room (similar to mom boss room)[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Curse of the Jamming[/td]
        [td]16% chance to respawn enemies after clearing room (except boss room)[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Curse of the Void[/td]
        [td]16% chance to reroll enemies and grid upon entering room[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Curse of the Bell[/td]
        [td]troll bombs is golden[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Curse of the Envy[/td]
        [td]other shop items disappear when you buy one [shop, black market, member card, devil deal, angel shop][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Curse of Poverty[/td]
        [td]greedy enemy tears. drop your coins when enemy tear hit you[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Curse of Carrion[/td]
        [td]turn normal poops into red[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Curse of the Bishop[/td]
        [td]16% chance to damage immunity. enemy will flash blue[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Curse of Montezuma[/td]
        [td]slippery ground, works only inside uncleared rooms[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Curse of Misfortune[/td]
        [td]-5 luck while curse is applied[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Curse of the Fool[/td]
        [td]16% chance to respawn enemies in cleared rooms (except boss room), doesn't close doors[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Curse of Secrets[/td]
        [td]hide secret/supersecret room doors when reentering room[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Curse of the Warden[/td]
        [td]all locked doors need 2 keys (Visual bug with door not applying chains on first door encounter. Door still require 2 keys)[/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td]Curse of the Desolation[/td]
        [td]50% chance to turn item into Item Wisp when touched. Add wisped item on next floor[/td]
    [/tr]
[/table] 

[hr][/hr] 
[h1] Commands: [/h1]
[code] eclipsed help  # get all console commands[/code] 
[code] eclipsed unlock all  # unlock all character marks and challenges[/code] 
[code] eclipsed reset all  # reset all character marks and challenges[/code]
[code] eclipsed curse [curse number]  # curses enable/disable[/code] 

[h1] Mod Compatibility: [/h1]
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=836319872&amp;searchtext=eid]EID[/url] (ENG and RUS)
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2376005362&amp;searchtext=encyclopedia]Encyclopedia[/url]

[h1] Info [/h1]
Repository: https://github.com/nazardz/eclipsed.git
Information about all mod features [url=https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1axmmCMAB0Qkk3u5EbAP3kxhZSDpbdk4mN674dQ37JmU/edit?usp=sharing]google table[/url] - may be outdated, so check it ingame with Encyclopedia. Also there is some of idea items and stuffs. Probably, I'll add the rest of them someday.

[b] Bug Reporting [/b]
If you’ve found some kind of bug, leave it on BUG REPORT

[b]NOT A BUG[/b]
Abihu and tainted Unbidden cannot fire tears by default.
Unbidden can get both items from More Options or from alt.path treasures
Unbidden - picking up a devil deal item does not affect the chance of an angel
Unbidden cannot pick up red hearts. even with bone hearts

[b] Contact [/b]
Discord: nineline#6596

Special Thanks to Kattack for helping to improve T.Unbidden</description>
    <version>1.40</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Active Items"/>
    <tag id="Trinkets"/>
    <tag id="Cards"/>
    <tag id="Pickups"/>
    <tag id="Player Characters"/>
    <tag id="Familiars"/>
    <tag id="Challenges"/>
</metadata>
